{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1500,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":11,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"si1270","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4377","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4392","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","title":"Information Security Awareness Quiz Back to School ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_3","title":"Take our Security Quiz to test your knowledge.   Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19016","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19034","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_106","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_201","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide4365","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","si4377","si4392","Text_Caption_2","Text_Caption_3","SmartShape_2","si19016","si19034","Text_Caption_106","Image_201"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4365"}}},{"id":"Image_217","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_217","roles":{}},{"id":"si12441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","roles":{}},{"id":"si12349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"1.  As summer vacation comes to an end, students and employees will be returning to school and work. Upon returning, many will need to either create new accounts or update passwords for existing accounts. What is the most important advice to always follow regarding passwords?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_328","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"Use a different password for each account ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Use a different password for each account\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si12382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"Make passwords long ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12382_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Make passwords long\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20585","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20589","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Combine upper and lower case ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20585_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Combine upper and lower case\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23460","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23464","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Include numbers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23460_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Include numbers\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","roles":{}},{"id":"si12459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_43","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19347","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19606","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19649","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19677","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19690","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"Correct - Answer:  A  Every day, online accounts are breached, with user names and passwords sold on the dark web. A hacker who gets your user name and password for one account will try it for numerous others because they count on the fact that people use the same password for multiple accounts.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  A  Every day, online accounts are breached, with user names and passwords sold on the dark web. A hacker who gets your user name and password for one account will try it for numerous others because they count on the fact that people use the same password for multiple accounts.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12483","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_217","si12349","si12364","si12386","si20589","si23464","si12459","si12473","si19347","si19361","si19593","si19606","si19621","si19634","si19649","si19662","si19677","si19690","si12429"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12483"},"question":{"interactionId":"12329","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1.  As summer vacation comes to an end, students and employees will be returning to school and work. Upon returning, many will need to either create new accounts or update passwords for existing accounts. What is the most important advice to always follow regarding passwords?\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_218","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_218","roles":{}},{"id":"si27079","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_910","roles":{}},{"id":"si26976","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_866","title":"2.  Many people will want to download apps for school or work to help them improve their efficiency. Are apps from a reputable ‘app store’ always safe to use? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26987","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_898","title":"1. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26991","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_899","title":"Yes ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26987_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_451","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26998","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_900","title":"2. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27002","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_901","title":"No ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26998_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_452","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si27073","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_909","roles":{}},{"id":"si27101","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_153","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27268q1","for":"Slide27268q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27119","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_154","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27268q1","for":"Slide27268q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27141","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_155","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27268q1","for":"Slide27268q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27159","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_156","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27268q1","for":"Slide27268q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27171","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27268q1","for":"Slide27268q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27183","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27268q1","for":"Slide27268q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27195","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27268q1","for":"Slide27268q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27207","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27268q1","for":"Slide27268q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27219","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27268q1","for":"Slide27268q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27268q1","for":"Slide27268q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27243","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27268q1","for":"Slide27268q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27255","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27268q1","for":"Slide27268q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27043","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_906","title":"Correct - Answer B  Many third-party apps are designed with the express purpose to collect user data and/or install malware unbeknownst to the owner of the device; that is why it is recommended to always procure your apps from a reputable ‘app store’ such as Google Play and Play Store.  Reputable companies have checks and policies in place that ensure a certain safety and quality in their product, however, even they do not guarantee that the app is safe to use.  There are still documented scams occurring within the best app stores and no app is safe to use if it is not kept up-to-date with patches to mitigate vulnerabilities.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27055","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_907","title":"Incorrect - Answer B  Many third-party apps are designed with the express purpose to collect user data and/or install malware unbeknownst to the owner of the device; that is why it is recommended to always procure your apps from a reputable ‘app store’ such as Google Play and Play Store.  Reputable companies have checks and policies in place that ensure a certain safety and quality in their product, however, even they do not guarantee that the app is safe to use.  There are still documented scams occurring within the best app stores and no app is safe to use if it is not kept up-to-date with patches to mitigate vulnerabilities.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_908","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide27268","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_218","si26976","si26991","si27002","si27101","si27119","si27141","si27159","si27171","si27183","si27195","si27207","si27219","si27231","si27243","si27255","si27067"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide27268"},"question":{"interactionId":"26956","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2.  Many people will want to download apps for school or work to help them improve their efficiency. Are apps from a reputable ‘app store’ always safe to use?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["2"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_219","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_219","roles":{}},{"id":"si26741","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_897","roles":{}},{"id":"si26638","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_865","title":"3.  If a student or employee returns to school or work and finds themselves victim to online bullying, what should they do with cyberbullying messages? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26649","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_885","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26653","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_886","title":"Reply nicely to the messages to befriend them ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26649_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_446","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Reply nicely to the messages to befriend them\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26660","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_887","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26664","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_888","title":"Trace them back to the sender and retaliate  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26660_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_447","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Trace them back to the sender and retaliate \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26671","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_889","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26675","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_890","title":"Record the messages and report them to appropriate authorities ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26671_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"448","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Record the messages and report them to appropriate authorities\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si26682","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_891","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26686","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_892","title":"Delete and ignore the messages ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26682_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"450","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Delete and ignore the messages\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26735","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_896","roles":{}},{"id":"si26763","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_149","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26930q2","for":"Slide26930q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26781","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_150","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide26930q2","for":"Slide26930q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26803","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_151","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide26930q2","for":"Slide26930q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26821","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_152","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide26930q2","for":"Slide26930q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26833","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26930q2","for":"Slide26930q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26845","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26930q2","for":"Slide26930q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26857","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide26930q2","for":"Slide26930q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26869","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide26930q2","for":"Slide26930q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26881","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide26930q2","for":"Slide26930q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26893","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide26930q2","for":"Slide26930q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26905","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide26930q2","for":"Slide26930q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26917","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide26930q2","for":"Slide26930q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26705","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_893","title":"Correct - Answers:  C  Bullies in general are not deterred by attempts to befriend them, and retaliation can escalate the conflict to more dangerous levels. Ignoring bullying is not always a realistic scenario because the victim can be left vulnerable to further bullying and harm. The best approach is to record the cyberbullying in as much detail as possible and to contact authorities. In Canada, cyberbullying can be reported to the RCMP, in addition, kids can call the Canada Kids Help Phone at 1-800-668-6868.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26717","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_894","title":"Incorrect - Answers:  C  Bullies in general are not deterred by attempts to befriend them, and retaliation can escalate the conflict to more dangerous levels. Ignoring bullying is not always a realistic scenario because the victim can be left vulnerable to further bullying and harm. The best approach is to record the cyberbullying in as much detail as possible and to contact authorities. In Canada, cyberbullying can be reported to the RCMP, in addition, kids can call the Canada Kids Help Phone at 1-800-668-6868.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26729","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_895","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide26930","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_219","si26638","si26653","si26664","si26675","si26686","si26763","si26781","si26803","si26821","si26833","si26845","si26857","si26869","si26881","si26893","si26905","si26917","si26729"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide26930"},"question":{"interactionId":"26618","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3.  If a student or employee returns to school or work and finds themselves victim to online bullying, what should they do with cyberbullying messages?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_220","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_220","roles":{}},{"id":"si26403","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_884","roles":{}},{"id":"si26300","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_864","title":"4.  As people head back to work many like to make new purchases (clothing, technology, etc.). What is the easiest method to learn if someone has made fraudulent charges on your bank or credit card accounts? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26311","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_872","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26315","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_873","title":"Wait until your card is rejected ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26311_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_440","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wait until your card is rejected\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26322","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_874","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26326","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_875","title":"Check the transactions regularly ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26322_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_441","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Check the transactions regularly\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si26333","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_876","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26337","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_877","title":"Wait until the bank contacts you ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26333_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"442","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wait until the bank contacts you\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26397","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_883","roles":{}},{"id":"si26425","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_145","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26592q3","for":"Slide26592q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26443","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_146","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide26592q3","for":"Slide26592q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26465","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_147","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide26592q3","for":"Slide26592q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26483","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_148","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide26592q3","for":"Slide26592q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26495","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26592q3","for":"Slide26592q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26507","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26592q3","for":"Slide26592q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26519","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide26592q3","for":"Slide26592q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26531","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide26592q3","for":"Slide26592q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26543","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide26592q3","for":"Slide26592q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26555","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide26592q3","for":"Slide26592q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26567","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide26592q3","for":"Slide26592q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26579","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide26592q3","for":"Slide26592q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26367","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_880","title":"Correct - Answer:  B  It is best if you can detect and report any fraud on your account as quickly as possible. You should check the transactions on your accounts regularly  by receiving statements, by using the ATM, by setting up telephone banking to get your balance and transactions, or via online banking. Many people rely solely on their cards so it is important to know they are safe.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26379","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_881","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  B  It is best if you can detect and report any fraud on your account as quickly as possible. You should check the transactions on your accounts regularly  by receiving statements, by using the ATM, by setting up telephone banking to get your balance and transactions, or via online banking. Many people rely solely on their cards so it is important to know they are safe.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26391","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_882","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide26592","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_220","si26300","si26315","si26326","si26337","si26425","si26443","si26465","si26483","si26495","si26507","si26519","si26531","si26543","si26555","si26567","si26579","si26391"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide26592"},"question":{"interactionId":"26280","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4.  As people head back to work many like to make new purchases (clothing, technology, etc.). What is the easiest method to learn if someone has made fraudulent charges on your bank or credit card accounts?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_221","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_221","roles":{}},{"id":"si27417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_923","roles":{}},{"id":"si27314","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_867","title":"5.  Books are an important part of school and work. Many people like to use book readers (Kindle or Kobo) which are a convenient way to have books available. How should you protect your e-book reader? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27325","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_911","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27329","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_912","title":"Use a sturdy cover ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27325_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_456","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Use a sturdy cover\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27336","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_913","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27340","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_914","title":"Put a passcode on it ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27336_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_457","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Put a passcode on it\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27347","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_915","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27351","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_916","title":"Put it airplane mode ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27347_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"458","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Put it airplane mode\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27358","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_917","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27362","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_918","title":"Only download e-books and apps from official and trusted sources ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27358_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"460","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Only download e-books and apps from official and trusted sources\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si28643","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28647","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28643_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si27411","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_922","roles":{}},{"id":"si27439","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_157","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27606q4","for":"Slide27606q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27457","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_158","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27606q4","for":"Slide27606q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27479","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_159","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27606q4","for":"Slide27606q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27497","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_160","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27606q4","for":"Slide27606q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27509","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27606q4","for":"Slide27606q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27521","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27606q4","for":"Slide27606q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27606q4","for":"Slide27606q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27545","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27606q4","for":"Slide27606q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27606q4","for":"Slide27606q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27569","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27606q4","for":"Slide27606q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27581","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27606q4","for":"Slide27606q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27606q4","for":"Slide27606q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27381","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_919","title":"Correct - Answer:  E  Anything portable can be dropped, rained on, etc. so a protective cover is worth the cost. Add a passcode  anyone who steals or finds your e-book reader cannot access your account (or your precious books) and put it in airplane mode when not downloading so it is not open to the internet and using battery power. Make sure to download e-books and apps from trusted sources as malware can be disguised in apps.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_920","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  E  Anything portable can be dropped, rained on, etc. so a protective cover is worth the cost. Add a passcode  anyone who steals or finds your e-book reader cannot access your account (or your precious books) and put it in airplane mode when not downloading so it is not open to the internet and using battery power. Make sure to download e-books and apps from trusted sources as malware can be disguised in apps.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_921","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide27606","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_221","si27314","si27329","si27340","si27351","si27362","si28647","si27439","si27457","si27479","si27497","si27509","si27521","si27533","si27545","si27557","si27569","si27581","si27593","si27405"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide27606"},"question":{"interactionId":"27294","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5.  Books are an important part of school and work. Many people like to use book readers (Kindle or Kobo) which are a convenient way to have books available. How should you protect your e-book reader?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_222","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_222","roles":{}},{"id":"si27755","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_937","roles":{}},{"id":"si27652","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_924","title":"6.  What it the most secure option to choose when logging onto a network to use Wi-Fi? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27663","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_925","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27667","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_926","title":"‘Private’ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27663_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_461","roles":{"answer":{"title":"‘Private’\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27674","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_927","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27678","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_928","title":"‘Home’ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27674_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_462","roles":{"answer":{"title":"‘Home’\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27685","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_929","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27689","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_930","title":"‘Public’ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27685_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"453_463","roles":{"answer":{"title":"‘Public’\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si27696","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_931","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27700","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_932","title":"‘Group’ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27696_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"455_464","roles":{"answer":{"title":"‘Group’\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27749","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_936","roles":{}},{"id":"si27777","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_161","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27944q5","for":"Slide27944q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27795","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_162","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27944q5","for":"Slide27944q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27817","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_163","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27944q5","for":"Slide27944q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27835","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_164","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27944q5","for":"Slide27944q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27847","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27944q5","for":"Slide27944q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27859","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27944q5","for":"Slide27944q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27871","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27944q5","for":"Slide27944q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27883","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27944q5","for":"Slide27944q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27895","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27944q5","for":"Slide27944q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27907","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27944q5","for":"Slide27944q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27919","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27944q5","for":"Slide27944q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27931","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27944q5","for":"Slide27944q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27719","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_933","title":"Correct - Answer:  C  By choosing ‘public’, the network assumes that you do not want to be ‘discoverable’ or share your files with anyone (like you may on a trusted private, home or work network); it defaults to the most secure settings by turning these options off (including Bluetooth).  Even if you have set up a ‘Homegroup’, it won’t be enabled on a ‘public’ computer.    Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27731","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_934","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  C  By choosing ‘public’, the network assumes that you do not want to be ‘discoverable’ or share your files with anyone (like you may on a trusted private, home or work network); it defaults to the most secure settings by turning these options off (including Bluetooth).  Even if you have set up a ‘Homegroup’, it won’t be enabled on a ‘public’ computer.    Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27743","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_935","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide27944","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_222","si27652","si27667","si27678","si27689","si27700","si27777","si27795","si27817","si27835","si27847","si27859","si27871","si27883","si27895","si27907","si27919","si27931","si27743"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide27944"},"question":{"interactionId":"27632","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6.  What it the most secure option to choose when logging onto a network to use Wi-Fi?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_223","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_223","roles":{}},{"id":"si28093","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_951","roles":{}},{"id":"si27990","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_938","title":"7.  Many people who return to work or school find themselves making new connections. Some do this by adding lots and lots of people to their social media accounts. Is this a good way for adults or kids to build a great social circle? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28001","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_939","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28005","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_940","title":"Yes ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28001_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_465","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si28012","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_941","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28016","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_942","title":"No ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28012_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_466","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si28087","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_950","roles":{}},{"id":"si28115","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_165","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide28282q6","for":"Slide28282q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28133","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_166","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide28282q6","for":"Slide28282q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28155","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_167","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide28282q6","for":"Slide28282q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28173","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_168","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide28282q6","for":"Slide28282q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28185","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide28282q6","for":"Slide28282q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28197","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide28282q6","for":"Slide28282q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28209","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide28282q6","for":"Slide28282q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28221","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide28282q6","for":"Slide28282q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28233","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide28282q6","for":"Slide28282q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28245","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide28282q6","for":"Slide28282q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28257","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide28282q6","for":"Slide28282q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28269","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide28282q6","for":"Slide28282q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28057","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_947","title":"Correct - Answer:  B  With social media scams and cybercriminals looking for any way to gain your personal information, the more friends you have, the more compromised you are likely to be.  With hundreds of ‘friends’ it is nearly impossible to know who all of them are.  Explain this to social media users in your family and remind them that “the safest user is a skeptical user”.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28069","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_948","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  B  With social media scams and cybercriminals looking for any way to gain your personal information, the more friends you have, the more compromised you are likely to be.  With hundreds of ‘friends’ it is nearly impossible to know who all of them are.  Explain this to social media users in your family and remind them that “the safest user is a skeptical user”.    Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28081","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_949","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide28282","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_223","si27990","si28005","si28016","si28115","si28133","si28155","si28173","si28185","si28197","si28209","si28221","si28233","si28245","si28257","si28269","si28081"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide28282"},"question":{"interactionId":"27970","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7.  Many people who return to work or school find themselves making new connections. Some do this by adding lots and lots of people to their social media accounts. Is this a good way for adults or kids to build a great social circle?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_224","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_224","roles":{}},{"id":"si28431","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_965","roles":{}},{"id":"si28328","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_952","title":"8.  As students and employees return to work and school many people will find themselves getting lots of emails. What are some indicators or a potential phishing email? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28339","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_953","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28343","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_954","title":"The email asks you to confirm personal information ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28339_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_469","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The email asks you to confirm personal information\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si28350","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_955","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28354","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_956","title":"The web and email address do not look genuine  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28350_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_470","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The web and email address do not look genuine \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si28361","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_957","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28365","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_958","title":"Its poorly written ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28361_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"442_471","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Its poorly written\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si28372","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_959","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28376","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_960","title":"There is a suspicious attachment ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28372_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"445_472","roles":{"answer":{"title":"There is a suspicious attachment\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si28658","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28658_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si28425","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_964","roles":{}},{"id":"si28453","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_169","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide28620q7","for":"Slide28620q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28471","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_170","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide28620q7","for":"Slide28620q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28493","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_171","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide28620q7","for":"Slide28620q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28511","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_172","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide28620q7","for":"Slide28620q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28523","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide28620q7","for":"Slide28620q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28535","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide28620q7","for":"Slide28620q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28547","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide28620q7","for":"Slide28620q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28559","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide28620q7","for":"Slide28620q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28571","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide28620q7","for":"Slide28620q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28583","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide28620q7","for":"Slide28620q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28595","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide28620q7","for":"Slide28620q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28607","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide28620q7","for":"Slide28620q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28395","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_961","title":"Correct - Answer:  E  Phishing emails can contain several red flags that can indicate it is not legitimate. The best way to spot the red flags is to slow down when checking emails and use a critical eye to analyse the content. Keep an eye out for emails requesting you to confirm personal information that you would never usually provide, such as banking details or login credentials. Web and email addresses are sometimes faked, if you take a moment to examine the email address you may find that it’s a bogus variation intended to appear authentic. Spelling mistakes could be a give away that an individual from another country is trying to scam you. Always examine attachments before clicking on them to avoid downloading something malicious.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28407","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_962","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  E  Phishing emails can contain several red flags that can indicate it is not legitimate. The best way to spot the red flags is to slow down when checking emails and use a critical eye to analyse the content. Keep an eye out for emails requesting you to confirm personal information that you would never usually provide, such as banking details or login credentials. Web and email addresses are sometimes faked, if you take a moment to examine the email address you may find that it’s a bogus variation intended to appear authentic. Spelling mistakes could be a give away that an individual from another country is trying to scam you. Always examine attachments before clicking on them to avoid downloading something malicious.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28419","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_963","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide28620","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_224","si28328","si28343","si28354","si28365","si28376","si28662","si28453","si28471","si28493","si28511","si28523","si28535","si28547","si28559","si28571","si28583","si28595","si28607","si28419"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide28620"},"question":{"interactionId":"28308","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8.  As students and employees return to work and school many people will find themselves getting lots of emails. What are some indicators or a potential phishing email?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_225","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_225","roles":{}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_227","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_227","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_5","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":"  Stay Current With   Information Security   By Subscribing to the    Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","si6231","Image_227","Button_4","si19054","si19068","Text_Caption_5","SmartShape_9"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":600},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"September2019Quiz","class":"project","title":"September2019Quiz","children":["Slide4365","Slide12483","Slide27268","Slide26930","Slide26592","Slide27606","Slide27944","Slide28282","Slide28620","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide12483q0","Slide27268q1","Slide26930q2","Slide26592q3","Slide27606q4","Slide27944q5","Slide28282q6","Slide28620q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":80,"passScore":64}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide4365","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide12483","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide27268","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide26930","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide26592","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide27606","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide27944","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide28282","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide28620","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 11"}]}